Oh, man...
It's seriously on its way over here.
What should I do?
I mean, what else can I do?
I guess I'll wait. His voice was so shaky.
Be careful. Make sure you
stay behind the umbrella.
This is Mob's power?
I don't believe he's doing this willingly.
He must've suffered some kind of shock,
sending his powers out of control.
“"Math Is Not Scary!” "Basic Drills English Vocabulary" "Future Aspirations” "Getting Along with Others"
"How to Ask Someone Out Awesomely" He must've suffered some kind of shock, sending his powers out of control.
“"Math Is Not Scary!” "Basic Drills English Vocabulary" "Future
Aspirations” "Getting Along with Others" "How to Ask Someone Out Awesomely"
“"Math Is Not Scary!” "Basic Drills English Vocabulary" "Future Aspirations” "Getting
Along with Others" "How to Ask Someone Out Awesomely" Serizawa, is that unusual?
“"Math Is Not Scary!” "Basic Drills English Vocabulary" "Future
Aspirations” "Getting Along with Others" "How to Ask Someone Out Awesomely"
“"Math Is Not Scary!” "Basic Drills English Vocabulary" "Future Aspirations”
"Getting Along with Others" "How to Ask Someone Out Awesomely" Sorry, what?!
Sorry, what?!
I don't think it is.
What's wrong, Serizawa?!
I'm sorry, Reigen-san. Let's turn back.
We came this far! What's gotten into you?!
It feels like my energy is being
stolen away at an alarming rate.
If this keeps up,
I won't be able to protect you.
We need to get away from here immediately.
In that case, go on and head back.
Huh?
I'll be fine on my own from here on out.
There's no way you'll be fine!
There's something I want
to talk to Mob about alone.
Let me go alone.
Reigen-san!
"Under Construction”
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
I realized that my youth was grey
The root of this irritation is unknown
My brain runs parallel with this emotional train
Struggling adolescence
Don't disturb the subconscious mind
Who's that behind me?
Opposing ideas, distortion
Purge the sorrow
So, do what you can now.
My life
Finally
Break it down!!
(WANT) desire (YOUNG) and sincerity
(BURN) they begin to sprout (1) within my chest
(TRANCE) I won't awaken (CHANCE) but I want to
(STANCE) both sides of the coin
(1) are back-to-back
Accept me as I am
Conflicting freedom and relations
If they can become one
That smile will be
One and only "1"
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
"Mob Psycho 100 "
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
I can't go to Tsubomi-chan like this.
If she ever saw me like this...
But this form is exactly what
Tsubomi-chan needs to see.
If she can still accept me,
I couldn't be happier.
Ever since Tsubomi-chan lost interest
in my powers, you stopped using them.
But that was the wrong decision.
You don't think changing yourself
for someone you love is natural?
I don't. At least, not when we're
talking about Tsubomi-chan.
You should try to remember why
you liked her in the first place.
It's because we got along...
No.
Tsubomi-chan didn't treat me any differently
even though I could use psychic powers.
She was kind to the both of us as a friend.
She accepted us.
It wasn't you that fell in love
with Tsubomi-chan...
It was me.
Mob!
Mob! Hey, Mob!
--Can you hear me? It's me!
--That's...
Master doesn't treat me any differently.
You can stop pretending now.
That man is a liar.
Mob!
Master has saved me so many times.
That's only because you were worth using.
That man is only interested in
using my powers for his work.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" Meaning he gave me
more different and more special treatment than anyone else.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
That's all there is between us.
But it'll all be okay now.
No stranger can tame me.
Once he sees my true form, he'll also...
Just look at him. That shocked face.
See? He's already frightened of me.
He can't even come over here.
Mob... Mob! Come back!
I had no idea...
...that this...
This is what you've been
holding in all this time?
And yet, I...
I had no idea...
I truly had no ideal
Master!
I'm sorry.
Mob?
Mob!
Wait!
I have something to say to you!
I have to...
Mob, please listen!
Please... I need to--
Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Mob!
I didn't want to lose to you...
Maybe you can be what you want to be
...so I was secretly working out, too!
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%,
6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27 %, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37 %, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
Just... listen to me for a bit.
No... I can't listen to him.
I've finally been freed.
"Seasoning Park"
I'll be able to see her soon...
Hey, Mob...
There's something I haven't been
able to tell you for a while now.
Wait...
Does he actually possess this much power?
There's something I need
to tell you right now...
...before you go see Tsubomi-chan.
Heya... You seem well.
It's been a while, Shigeo.
Shigeo.
Because you've been waiting
for me deep down inside,
it looks like I wasn't destroyed after all.
And then I was able to come back because
I was drawn into this spiral of power.
Partner, let's hear what Reigen has to say.
I just happened to run
into Dimple over there.
And because of that, we made it in time.
Hey, no time to chitchat, buddy.
I'm basically giving it my all
right now to literally exist.
Yeah, it seems like it.
Dimple, I know you just saved me and all...
...but could you give us a minute?
What? The hell are you gonna do?!
Tch. Fine, then.
Don't you start fighting, though.
Mob.
I--- I---
I don't...
...have any spiritual... or psychic powers...
I don't have any powers!
I never did!
"Seasoning Park"
It was a lie.
It was a lie... from the start.
Oh, excuse me. My allergies.
I lie a lot.
To my customers... and to you.
The first day that you came to my office...
...I lied to you.
I heard you out, thinking I had some idea
of what you were going through.
But you believed me so easily.
That's why, from that day on,
until today... I've been...
"Spiritual Consultation” That's why, from
that day on, until today... I've been...
That's why, from that day on,
until today... I've been...
I've been using you this entire time.
The truth is...
I don't know a damn thing...
...about psychic powers.
This is...
...the real me.
I'm sorry that I acted like
your master the whole time.
But let me just say one last thing!
This doesn't make you different or special.
Everyone has another side to them.
Even me!
So you don't need to worry so much.
Actually... I guess it's okay to worry.
Because that's also just
a natural thing to do.
Just between you and me, I absolutely
despise the other side I'm hiding...
But it's because of my lies
that you came into my life.
And you're who you are today
because of your powers, aren't you?
Er... What I'm trying to say here is...
You're fine... just the way you are.
You don't need me anymore.
You'll be fine.
Just go ahead and accept yourself already.
You'll be able to do that
because you're you, Mob.
I know you can!
You heard what Master said.
Are you telling me that
you're going to accept me?
No... I want you to accept me, too.
Just like everyone else did.
And you're okay with that...? Really?
Let's go back to how things used to be.
Wait...
What if she turns you down?
It'll be okay.
Come on.
Let's go.
"Kageyama"
"Shigeo"
"Kageyama Shigeo"
Dimple, let him go alone.
Is Tsubomi-chan even waiting for him?
Mob's the only one who needs to know that.
Reigen, what are you gonna do from now on?
Beats me.
Like you can talk, though.
Your color seems more muted now.
Hey, he's coming back.
I guess she wasn't there.
I mean, who can blame her?
She rejected me.
What?!
She was actually waiting there?
She said that she still has yet
to see me in that way...
I see.
But, hey, things like this happen.
Yeah, it's okay.
At least she was actually waiting for you.
Things are just getting started for you.
Right...
And, you know... we're gonna have
to repair this city somehow.
But don't you worry.
I'm sure everyone will help out.
Oh, I know. That one guy
who fixed your house before.
We can call him over.
You know plenty of other psychics, too.
I'll call Serizawa, too.
Oh, Serizawa?
Yeah, I'm totally fine. No worries.
More importantly, could you come over here?
"Confession
~The Future~"
"Body Improvement Club"
Kageyama-senpai!
"Goals for October"
"Goals for October" It's time to go
running! Captain Sagawa's calling for you.
"Goals for October"
Okay, I'll be right there!
So, yeah, leave your schedule
open at the end of the year.
I'll be going with you guys this year.
Sure. I'll look forward to it.
I wonder if the UFO will come again.
There's no doubt about it.
It'll come.
Body Improvement!
Fight on! Fight on! Fight on!
It's been six months since you've joined.
Everyone's running a lot better now.
Last year, I'd get anemic pretty quickly,
but I was able to get this far
thanks to everyone else.
So let's all help each other out
when things get rough.
Right!
How are things going lately?
Is it rough being the vice president?
I guess it depends on how motivated I am.
I'm starting to understand that the senpais
before us were pretty ambitious.
How are you doing as the vice captain?
We have a lot of members now,
so it's really fun.
Next week, we're going to a training boot
camp with Musashi-senpai and the others.
Oh, yeah.
Your younger brother looked like
he had some promising muscles.
Why doesn't he join us, Kageyama?
What do you think?
No, I'm pretty busy with being vice
president, so I'm gonna pass.
--You okay?
--Yeah.
Be careful!
Th-Thank goodness.
What are you even doing, Nii-san?
Heya, Kageyama brothers.
Teru-san.
It's been a while. Are you heading
over there, too, Hanazawa-kun?
Yeah, let's head over together.
But, man, I've been so bored lately.
Want to go shopping again?
I heard the newest addition
to the Hagemon line is out.
Sure, let's go.
What?! He's gonna wear that T-shirt again?!
I-I need to actually stop him this time.
I need to tell him it's okay
to wear whatever he wants!
Nii-san...
Did you want to go check out the
new Hagemon with us, too, Ritsu?
Er, no... I'm busy with
vice president duties, so...
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" Er,
no... I'm busy with vice president duties, so...
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
I really love that T-shirt.
Really?
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
Hello.
Oh, there he is.
Hey, you three.
Come on in and have a seat.
Here, have some tea.
Thank you for calling Spirits
and Such Consultation Office.
--Looks like Serizawa-san's gotten used to the job.
--You'd like to discuss this matter over the phone?
--Yeah, he's doing great.
--Right... right... Oh, no, no...
--Well, he's the backbone of this agency.
It's been six months since
I started working here as well.
Aren't I starting to look the part?
So how are things going with
you and your girlfriend?
Sh-She's not my girlfriend! She rejected me...
They talk on the phone every now and then.
Oh, excellent.
Ritsu!
President Kurata, we're here!
Oh, there was someone else at the entrance.
They might be a client.
Huh?
Who the...?
I invited them.
Oh, I invited someone I know, too.
That's okay, right?
Hey, Serizawa. How've you been, man?
Suzuki!
Hey, Ritsu! It's been a while.
He's coming!
President Kurata, he'll be here any second!
There was a blue light shining
O-Okay! Okay, everyone! Hide!
There was a blue light shining "The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen
Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office" O-Okay! Okay, everyone! Hide!
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen Arataka's Spirits
and Such Consultation Office" O-Okay! Okay, everyone! Hide!
I'm wide awake this 1:30 AM "The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen
Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office" O-Okay! Okay, everyone! Hide!
I'm wide awake this 1:30 AM "The New Star of the 21st Century
Reigen Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen
Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
Just like a sudden bruise out of nowhere "The New Star of the 21st
Century Reigen Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
Just like a sudden bruise out of nowhere
The outline of the pain faintly appears
Man, I'm wiped.
Yokai, my ass.
I held on to it as I was losing it
It was just some old dude with a butt chin.
This slightly embarrassing new page
What remained even after I swiped
What remained even after I swiped They kept nagging me
to do an exorcism, so I just randomly spread some salt.
They kept nagging me to do an exorcism,
so I just randomly spread some salt.
Are the smiles of my friends right beside me They kept nagging
me to do an exorcism, so I just randomly spread some salt.
Are the smiles of my friends right beside me
Isn't that what you always do?
Huh? The lights're off...
Hey, Serizawa! Tome-chan?
Anyone here?
Yes, I want someone to understand...
This wish that's hidden colorless and invisible
The breath I was holding deep within my heart
Happy birthday, Reigen-san!
I let it all out at once and return to my senses
On days that I'm feeling apathetic it suddenly
comes to mind Happy birthday, Reigen-san!
On days that I'm feeling apathetic
it suddenly comes to mind
These seasons I spent as if they were a given
Even if reality becomes sullied
"Happy Birthday Reigen Arataka"
Even if reality becomes sullied "Happy Birthday
Reigen Arataka" Happy birthday, Master Reigen.
Even if reality becomes sullied
Happy birthday, Master Reigen.
Happy birthday,
Master Reigen.
Only the sky we saw together is
real Happy birthday, Master Reigen.
Only the sky we saw together is real
Mob...
Go on. Blow out the candles.
This is more incomprehensible
Hey, your eyes seem kinda red.
Than the grammar on the blackboard
Y-You dumb-ass! Dimple!
If it's going to disappear within 24 hours
What? You gonna cry, Reigen-san?
This flowing story is just too lonely
What?!
I just can't do it
I just can't do it Aren't I a capable
secretary? Now raise my pay.
Aren't I a capable secretary?
Now raise my pay.
Just like that back hip circle I gave up on
Aren't I a capable secretary? Now raise my pay.
Aren't I a capable secretary?
Now raise my pay.
But I'm not going to... Aren't I a
capable secretary? Now raise my pay.
But I'm not going to...
Oh, no! My cake!
Give up
My present anymore
Oh, no! My cake!
I adorn my overflowing emotions
And run through my worries and hesitations
It can't be decided from 0 to 100
Draw the incomplete future with this hand
We can't even prove its existence
But as the world stabs the middle of my chest
Hey! Who just did that?!
It overflows with cobalt blue
It overflows with cobalt blue Aw, that
sucks. I sorta wanted to see you cry.
Aw, that sucks.
I sorta wanted to see you cry.
True blue... Aw, that sucks. I
sorta wanted to see you cry.
True blue...
There's a client heading here right now!
What? I-Is there?
True blue...
You're all going to be helping me!
"Mob Psycho 100 III" English Translator: Michelle Tymon Translation
Editor: Zachary Carlysle Translation Checker: Sriram Gurunathan